Finally, let's take a look at its chain here.
Oh, so you guys are more concerned about this...
No, let's talk about this first.
This Marvelous Designer account
is because the name is too long.
Bilibili doesn't let you pass.
So we can only call it Soshie.
And when we named this Soshie,
because we already had this app earlier,
and because it's a Korean app,
so when we named it, we probably didn't think about this Soshie.
Is it easy to stretch this version that controls the strength of the gold chain?
The lower the strength of the gold chain,
the easier it is to stretch.
Because it's easier to stretch,
the whole fabric is elastic enough,
so it's also softer.
It's more like a hammer.
It's more close to the body.
For example,
you can understand that it's easier to stretch.
It can be counted as the stretch rate.
But it and the gold chain,
uh,
But it and the gold chain
The gold chain is more tight.
You have to figure out the gold chain is more tight.
The gold chain strength is the gold chain strength of the fabric.
This is my doubt.
The little friend who sent the chat,
Are you my colleague?
How can you name it?
And here you can pay attention to how I made this chain.
First of all, I made this chain, I used fabric to replace the chain.
This chain is in the form of a topstitch, that is, it is attached to the top of the board.
So you can see that the board I made is a translucent board.
Finally, I reduced the transparency of this board to 0.
It is an invisible board, you can only see the chain.
Okay, here I will reserve a little bit of conflict thickness first.
Because when we add this, when we add the name line, the name line is not involved in the simulation.
So when we add this, when we add the name line, the name line is not involved in the simulation.
Because when we add this, when we add the name line, the name line will be inter retailed.
It looks a little fake, so we must reserve the depth of the name line.
So here I set it to strawberry third.
You can look that when I simulate, I will let this best.
Because when you are doing the simulation, you can't see the name line, the name line is not involved in the simulation, you can only see the position of the name line when you stop.
So just remind everyone, remember to reserve some of this for him to come out.
Then about this chain, how do you adjust your width and length?
First of all, when we are doing the name line, the OBJ name line, because this is a chain made by an OBJ name line.
Then the name line is attached to the top of the board.
So, so here we have to pay attention to the width and length of the chain and the length of the chain is adjusted by the value of the name line.
Then this name line, it is a single loop, it is a single loop structure, that is to say, you just do half and half, as long as it can be connected.
So you can see that I am here at the end is half of it, have you seen it?
Hello, hello, yes, we started the broadcast, but we are about to end the broadcast.
You can see that the structure here at the end is actually half of it, have you seen it?
So my single loop is usually from here to here, my single loop is from here to here.
Do a single loop like this to make sure it can be connected.
Do you understand?
Then you just add it up.
Just select the name line here.
We switch to the name line here.
After switching to the name line, select the type of name line below.
There is a self-defined OBJ here.
Put this single loop OBJ file into the self-defined OBJ here, click on it, and open your OBJ.
Another thing to note is that although you are going to import this single loop OBJ,
but I recommend everyone because our self-defined OBJ is used.
Yes, it is real.
You can see that it is three-dimensional.
It will also reflect metal light.
This is done by OBJ.
So what about this file?
Where did I just talk about?
Oh, the self-defined OBJ.
And then, because our self-defined OBJ, its unit is done using the logic of Marvelous Designer.
So this OBJ, you'd better import it into Marvelous Designer first.
And then, the unit is set to mm.
So one unit is set to mm.
And then, you select the definition, and it is set to OBJ.
Do you understand?
Otherwise, if your unit is set to mm,
and then you import it to Marvelous Designer and use the self-defined name line,
its unit will be understood as the unit of mm.
In the end, you may be able to change it to the correct size through some of the obvious settings,
but its grid has already transformed.
You will see some broken faces.
This is why some people will say when they self-define OBJ,
why my OBJ is fine in other computers,
but I have a broken face in Marvelous Designer.
It's because your unit is different from the default limit unit of Marvelous Designer.
And the default mm unit is different.
And for this unit,
you can edit Marvelous Designer,
the unit in the entire software is not affected.
It doesn't affect the name line setting,
because it has the logic behind it.
So if you find that there is a broken face,
the easiest way is to
import this file,
import it to Marvelous Designer,
and then use mm as the unit,
and export it again.
And this OBJ file,
after you import it to Marvelous Designer,
remember to put it on the ground,
to observe if it has a broken face problem.
It doesn't have a broken face.
Then we confirm that its unit is mm,
and you can export it.
When exporting,
you can just use the unit's unit number.
You can import the unit according to the unit you set.
Do you understand?
Let's go back to this.
Of course,
this is a relatively simple way to use fabric to solve these chains.
Yes,
this chain,
my entanglement is done with fabric.
Use fabric plus a fixed needle,
and then fix it to the current one.
It's on this position.
I was going to make a big chain knife,
and then wrap this chain around the big chain knife outside.
But because it doesn't fit with the overall cute image of Hana,
although I like this kind of setting,
but it's okay to think about it.
Yes,
then let's take a look at its chain here.
First,
you go to adjust the name,
the length of the name line.
Yes,
you,
because,
because you put the chain knife in the shape of your model,
and then you put the fabric on the outside,
it's like putting the chain on the outside,
and then you fold the name line up,
and that's it.
So in fact,
using the name line is just to say,
just to wear,
that is,
you're wearing a chain.
Ask the Marvelous Designer how to make chains.
You can see the link in the description.
We have it in the description.
This fabric,
and then you add the name line,
and then you fit the name line on this fabric.
In the circuitry simulation,
you use,
you use a fixed needle,
and then go,
go,
adjust it.
Just how do you do that,
how do you do that,
How do you make the fabric for the knot?
You just need to wrap the needle around the fabric
If you can't do it, you can watch our Bandai video
Hello everyone, good evening
The thickness and length of the thread are used to adjust the properties of the thread
In the end, we can adjust it
Let's take a look
For example, this is the chain
And then
If you adjust its length
For example, we adjust the length to 10
It will be more tightly arranged along here
And the thickness of the thread is the width in this direction
For example, this is 10
It will be more tightly arranged along here
Do you understand?
Let me show you again
To put it simply
This
This is the chain
This is a piece of fabric
Its transparency is 0
Now this is a complete half
Then I use this
I use a fixed needle to fix its position
Then slowly wrap it around the model's hand
After wrapping
Ok
Let's delete this thread first
After wrapping
Let's switch to the thread menu here
After switching, select this thread
Then define an OBJ
Define an OBJ for it
This OBJ is a single loop
It's a single loop OBJ
It can connect to itself
Connect to itself
After it is a single loop
After we define it
It's also what I said earlier
Remember to set the unit
Then after we have defined it
Then we put it on here with the modern thread tool
Ok
After putting it on
Now there is a piece
This
Part like a chain
It is a three-dimensional structure
This single loop is also a three-dimensional OBJ
After adjustment
Then we go to the fabric
In the fabric
Then set its transparency to 0
Now you understand, right?
Oh, it's still like this
This is equivalent to you using the fabric to control a chain operation
Well, you can make a rope
I have also made a necklace
Pearl necklace is also made like this
There was also in the previous video
Isn't it amazing?
But there is one thing to note
If you can stretch
Because it is attached to the top of the net grid
This
This also shows that
If your net grid stretching is very, very serious
If your net grid stretching is very serious
This thread will deform
Do you understand?
Oh, the recording is in our
Marvelous Designer's
This official account
Will be broadcasted later
No, today's teaching video
Isn't today's live broadcast here?
Do you have anything to do with this project file?
And in the process of using Marvelous Designer
What else?
Is there anything you don't understand?
Ah, I didn't want to go down
I'm asking what's wrong
It's not hard, it's not hard
What's wrong with everyone using Marvelous Designer?
You can also add our
But because today's live broadcast is over
It's going to be off
So
I don't think it'll be watching QQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQQ
I don't think you'll watch it
Ha ha ha
Modeling for size
It's like this
It's
Um, in the process of modeling
The process of modeling
This
How to say
It's that your board shape is reasonable
And for the size, if you want it to be irregular, or if you want it to have a difference in size, then you have to make it a different length.
If you want it to be more flat, with no creases, then you have a higher requirement for the board shape.
Yes, the second group is full now.
3D tool, blue, count the third tool.
This question is what you asked, right? I've already talked about this question before, it's like this.
Let's just look at this model.
For example, this is a board, right?
And then we copy and paste.
Here.
Okay, copy and paste.
And then we create a
Then if we use this tool to run these two boards, you will see that this board will first become semi-transparent, and then you will choose another board.
The types of floating lines between them will automatically change to TURN.
This tool only has this one way to use it.
The second group will not replace people at the moment.
If you are interested, you can add our third group or first group.
Is it necessary to make a three-dimensional board?
Everyone is doing three-dimensional.
It depends on what type you are doing.
Of course, you have the foundation of the board shape, which is definitely better.
It's just that you were just in the whole live broadcast.
What I hope everyone can understand is that even if you don't know how to make a board, you can do it.
If you don't know how to make a board, it's not a very important problem.
Because you can continue to test and adjust.
Cut off the excess.
Then fill in the shortcomings.
This is all adjusted little by little.
The board is in Maya Top.
Every board point has to merge.
Is there any good way?
No.
Hahaha.
If you don't understand the type of floating line, you can do it.
If you don't understand, you can take a look at our skill sharing video.
If you don't understand, you can watch the skill sharing video.
I've already posted this.
I posted it before.
Oh, the password of the group is Hana.
If you pay attention to our Marvelous Designer Bilibili account,
the background will send you a private message.
The way to add a group.
It looks like this.
Then I'll give it to you.
Anyway, I've demonstrated it.
Let's talk about it.
These two boards are a little big.
Let's shrink it a little bit.
These are two boards, right?
If it's on air, I'll talk about it when I get back to work.
It's going to be on vacation these days.
Okay, let's print the board first.
Wait a minute.
Let's draw the board like this.
This is a board.
And then we put it on.
After that, let's sew the side.
Of course, don't overlap the boards.
Sew it.
After that, simulate it.
Now they are on the same side, right?
This place is connected, right?
And then if we change its sewing line type to TURN,
it will flatten.
See?
If it is flattened, it can prevent some seams from stabilizing.
Do you understand?
No.
I'm in China.
I'm in Shanghai.
So I'm on vacation in China.
Do you understand?
For the number of groups, you can look at the private messages.
For private messages, I will private message all three groups to everyone.
Which group is free, you can add which group.
In fact, you don't have to add each group.
Because what I say in each group is not much different.
Well, anyway, if you start a live broadcast, you can pay attention.
If you pay attention to our Bilibili account,
you will know when there will be a live broadcast.
Do you understand?
Well, what else do you have in the process of using Marvelous Design?
The WeChat official account is MarvelousDesignerCN.
Yes.
So if you don't understand these questions,
you can take a look at our tips and share video.
There are tips and share videos in it.
And our...
This...
Written manuscript...
What is that called?
Special column.
There is a special column in Bilibili.
Do you understand?
Okay, okay.
Do you think it's convenient to make hand-made clothes?
How to say?
I know some people make hand-made clothes with Marvelous Design.
But it depends.
In fact, hand-made clothes are also part of the material.
And then, hand-made clothes have some very anti-gravity effects.
If you use Marvelous Design,
if you want me to do it, it's okay.
But some special effects,
it may not be able to make such anti-gravity effects like other hand-made software.
I don't open classes.
I am the champion of anti-discrimination.
If I don't have time for work,
I am...
I basically don't do these related content.
So I usually, even if I open classes,
I also open classes as an official member.
Of course, this time I made this dress,
it is also a little reference.
Hand-made clothes may be used.
For example, I think the overall texture of this shirt is more like hand-made clothes.
But hand-made clothes usually have this kind of softer pleats.
At the same time, it will have more sharp pleats.
What about this kind of pleats?
First of all, you can use the inner line to do it.
But the effect may not be particularly good.
Of course,
if you know other 3D software,
you can combine it and use it.
It's not that you can only use one of Manless Designer.
Everyone knows some other 3D software, right?
Thank you for your support.
As for this fabric,
its physical properties,
you can take a look at our live broadcast at the beginning of this live broadcast.
There is a prize over there.
HANA.
H A N A.
If you follow our Bilibili account,
you will know.
Or you can send a private message,
it will also reply to your family.
Speaking of common fabrics,
my most common one is
Paul Sotafita.
This is a blouse.
I often use it to make this kind of hard jacket effect.
And then,
there is also,
uh,
a custom fabric.
Because I prefer to use custom fabric.
I usually use hand-stitched fabric.
Uh,
now the mainstream trend is,
oh, wait,
the fabric is not finished yet.
And then the pants are
Cotton Garbden.
Uh,
the fabric is
used to make pants and suits.
And also,
a thick shirt.
Yes,
after the fabric is disassembled,
the fabric carving is still inseparable.
Because some effects,
some effects,
it,
because in Marvelous Designer,
what we pay more attention to is
some more practical
fabric disassembly.
The fabric in it and in reality
are more linked.
So,
some of them are more
fantasy or
more special structure.
Uh,
you just rely on fabric disassembly,
it may not be able to do it.
Even if it can,
you may not,
that is,
you are not sure
how to modify and adjust
some of these values.
And,
for example,
to set some weight,
or to set density,
or to complete it through
some special means.
For example,
like pressure,
to give it
a shape.
These can be combined.
Uh,
MD's OBJ into DAS,
without MD's material,
you can see
in your UV editor,
have you put the UV well?
In the UV editor,
uh,
you can see that
there is no need
to use the material
after translation,
or less after translation.
It's like this.
It's just that
my personal
habit is
to make things
in the English environment.
So,
I won't use
the material
after translation.
Thank you,
Zheng Qi.
Thank you, Zheng Qi,
for the lucky medicine
that you chose.
Thank you.
But,
you don't need
to give gifts.
Uh,
thank you,
but you don't need
to give gifts.
Thank you.
Uh,
the mainstream...
Oh,
right.
Let's go back
and take a look.
Which kind of
fabric is better
for ancient cloth?
You can use
Yama,
because,
uh,
ancient people
wear more cotton
clothes.
Or,
you can use
softer
cotton
fabrics.
Uh,
the mainstream...
The mainstream...
Are you talking about
the working process?
Is the fabric
after translation
less?
No,
it's not.
If it's less,
it means
this fabric
has the same
physical properties
as the other
fabrics.
The only difference
between them
is the difference
between the stickers.
In our software,
although you may
have many fabrics
at the same time,
some of them
have the same physical properties.
Uh,
if you want to
talk about
other software,
actually,
I don't really care.
You can talk about
them.
But,
from my point of view,
because we've seen
a lot of users,
it's not necessarily...
How to say it?
For individual users,
there are a lot
of different
types of
software
they use.
Can Marvelous 3's
virtual character
model be
used for
commercial use?
Uh,
yes,
it can.
My
personal opinion
is that
it can be used
for commercial use.
I remember
it can be used
for commercial use.
Uh,
but,
uh,
before I talk about
the mainstream
and non-mainstream
issues,
um,
generally speaking,
if you're
in a company,
then,
what I see
a lot
is Maya
and these
things.
But,
actually,
to put it bluntly,
everyone is
working
in a company.
So,
what software
do you want
to use?
What software
is useful
in their
workflow?
If you
have
this
software
skill,
it's also
helpful
for you.
Or,
usually,
um,
if you
learn
a little,
it's definitely
not bad for you,
right?
But,
if the client
has a special
design,
then I don't know
what kind of
design your client
has.
I'm at Marvelous
Designer.
Where can I be?
Um?
Ah?
Yes,
you have to use
Maya,
Max,
MD,
ZB.
In fact,
many game companies
use our software.
We also
know this.
In terms of
material
processing,
our software
is more
um,
more
authoritative.
Um.
I'm a
community
manager.
I'm in charge
of
managing
Chinese
communities
and
doing technical
support
and training.
No, I work in Shanghai.
Yes.
Is there anything else
you're curious about
Marvelous Designer?
Yes.
Marvelous Designer
is a Korean software.
Don't think that
because
we're more active
on Bilibili,
we're more
popular,
then
you'll think
we're a Chinese software.
No.
But I'm Chinese.
Chinese people,
Chinese soul.
Haha.
Um.
Let me see.
Any other questions?
Um.
Although,
you have to understand,
I saw
there was one
saying that
Han people
usually use
silk.
You have to understand
that
silk
is
the
material
of
silk.
And
then
the texture
of silk
is another thing.
Do you know?
Um.
I think
this is
our
Oh.
You said Marvelous Designer
has this
self-defined
position.
This thing
is
um.
How to say?
Um.
I didn't
mention
the
development
requirements
of this
thing.
But
this
is
a
little bit
complicated.
But
there is
not
a lot
of
feedback
saying
that
it needs
this function.
So its
priority
is quite
thick.
Yes.
The
sticker of
silk
is one
thing.
The
texture of
silk itself
is another
thing.
Because
many people
think that silk
is very
soft.
But
in fact,
silk
is not
very
stretchable
in many
cases.
Sometimes
it is
very
stretchable
for
sewing
fabrics.
But sometimes
you also
think that silk
feels light.
But in
fact,
its stretchability
may not be
very good.
You still
have to think about the
stretchability.
Is there any
good
way to
make clothes
for Marvelous
Designer?
You can
take a look at
the video
we made
before.
Oh,
that's
it.
Self-determination
position.
Well,
okay.
Then I
can
mention
the
function
development
needs
of
self-determination
position
.
Let me
record it.
But because of
the
calculation
in our
software,
because it is
the first
one,
it is the
function of gravity.
Because I'm not
sure if this is
developed well.
I just
thought about it.
I think that
our position
is a
vertical
downward
gravity
function.
So I'm not
sure if
changing
its direction
will cause
a lot
of
bugs
and
make it
difficult
to
develop.
If you
don't know
the
properties,
it
does
need
some
time
to
get
started.
Wait a minute.
Let me think about it.
Let's put
the
chat
here.
Every
option
in the
material property
,
you don't
care about
what it is.
If you
want to
predict
what it is,
you can
go to
the
Chinese prediction
video.
It will
have
additional
learning materials.
You can
just
look at
the
table
of
the
negative
value.
Or you can
add a group
and ask
where these
tables
go.
There will
be friends
replying to
you.
Then,
if you
don't know
how to
learn
MD,
I can't
tell
if
you
can
do it
or not.
If you
don't know
how
to
modify
it,
then you
can
do it
very quickly.
Or in
Marvelous
Atlanta,
you have
to do
a large
model very
quickly.
Because the
large model
is very
fast.
You have
a lot
of
time to
modify it.
So,
you have
to
do it
very
quickly.
It is
just
like
the
basic
material
of
MD
software.
That's
it.
Have you
considered
this
function?
If you
send
the
physical
material
of
MD software
to
another
brother software,
CLO,
you can
check out
CLO's
official
account if
you are
interested.
However,
if you
are not
in the
fashion
industry,
even if
you
buy
the
physical
material,
you still
can't
feel
the
texture
of
the
material.
Then,
you can
manually
modify it.
I won't
look at
this one.
I won't
go back.
Well,
if you
have
a
specific
position,
MD
doesn't
add
the
tissue function.
CLO is
another
software
in our
company.
If you
have
a specific
position,
you can
modify it.
Because
the
function
development
needs
are not
exactly
what
you
want.
It's
not
that
each
function
development
requirement
that we
suggest
is
considered
to be
an
important
option.
So if the evaluation is very important, then we will definitely take the initiative to start developing
But if the feedback is not so positive, not so much, and its development is relatively difficult, then it may not be very easy to develop
This is a video that explains the attribute of fabric preview
This is what I just said, look at the previous Chinese preview
You are a fashion designer, you want to customize your own pose
Shift X can choose to adjust Google, and if you are a fashion designer
Then your feedback should be mentioned by Cloe
Not by me
But by Marvelous Designer
Why doesn't Marvelous Designer have a rendering function?
Because we...
Just no
Because everyone has a different rendering request
Usually there are already mainstream rendering tools
Marvelous Designer is more inclined to do a whole workflow
Instead of replacing some software
That has already been opened
So we don't have a plan to add a rendering function
Do you have any other questions?
We're almost done at 11.30
There is a high quality mode, but the high quality mode is not able to produce pictures
The texture of the controller is...
This is what you need to have a certain understanding of physical properties
To be able to make more precise adjustments
So you have to learn more about physical properties videos
And then you have to practice more on your own
Marvelous Designer to other software
Which software is currently supported by the insertion of which software?
There is only one
A special feature that is available in the
One Arcade
If you have the ability to develop other inserts
We are also welcome to develop an insert
Function Supervision of individual options
You can take a look at our preprocessing materials
Physical properties videos
The direction of interaction with other three software
As we mentioned before, we are currently working on the UI and UI connection.
Oh, Kass's original details?
There is no way to do that.
It's a battle between the modder and the original artist.
It's not something you can solve in a day or two.
Because the scene behind my last drawing is actually a scene from the UI map.
As for the other details related to the UI,
I can't go into too much detail.
Because this...
These details will probably be removed by me when I upload this video.
Do you think adding the brush function can solve the problems between them?
It's a pity that it doesn't.
Because we have the sculpt function in our software.
But it's not that useful.
It's usable, but not that useful.
Even in our software, we have developed the corresponding dynamic folding brush function.
I can only say that it's usable.
If you want to join MD officially, you can submit your resume.
You can submit your resume, whether you send it to me or through...
Yes.
Whether you send it to me through me or through the backstage.
Anyway, if you are particularly interested in joining MD,
you can send your resume to sherry at marvellousdesigner.com.
The music of the original drawing and the modeling is indeed not something that can be solved with a brush.
Because when the original drawing was being drawn,
many of the strokes were done with one stroke.
She thought that the strokes would look better this way.
But in fact, when we were doing the remodeling and modeling,
I can only say that it was very creative.
We are not 996.
No, we don't work very hard.
Currently, in China,
I am the only one who deals with community.
In terms of AI, I don't think AI can replace many of the original drawings.
Because AI is...
As far as I can see,
I don't think AI can replace many of the original drawings.
But AI is...
Everyone is saying that it can be used.
But I think...
It's not a good tool.
It's not a good tool to replace some of the original drawings.
But now,
many people are saying that
AI can replace some of the original drawings.
Or it can save some of the original drawings.
Or...
The way I think about this now is always...
I think it can replace some of the original drawings.
I don't think so.
This is a tool that can help everyone to work better.
I know what she's talking about.
That AI...
That...
It's...
The whole...
I don't know what she was talking about.
This doll has a hoop.
What can it come from?
The whole...
Because I feel everyone
doesn't have to be such nhiều about it.
First,
AI is out.
Don't we have to continue with the idea of not taking mothers,
we don't have to,
It's just a tool
Not hard at all
How did I join MD company?
If you are interested in these questions, you can add them to the Q&A
In our live stream, you don't have to ask about my personal stuff
If you don't have any questions, let's call it a day
I'm getting ready to go home
If you have any other questions, you can talk to me in the Q&A
Thank you for your support
It's late, thank you for your company
I hope I can keep you company
Bye bye
That's it for today's live stream
Bye bye everyone
Yes, I'm at the company right now
I'm going home by taxi
Thank you everyone, bye bye
Happy National Day, thank you everyone
Everyone, you must rest well during National Day
Don't roll up your sleeves
Bye bye everyone, good night
Thank you for your support
Remember to follow our Bilibili account, MD official
Bye bye everyone
Thank you for your support
Thank you, thank you
I hope everyone can rest well and take care of your health
Bye everyone, bye bye
Bye bye